我们，是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文！
and Steven!
光畸变的探险
翻译
presisco
校对
BBBB
特效
CCCC
压制
DDDD
这不可能
This can't be happening.
史蒂文，你回来了！
Steven, you're back.
嘿，史蒂仔
Hey, Steve-O.
我们对之前的事非常抱歉
We're so sorry about earlier.
别管这些了！
Forget that!
我们必须追上她！
We have to catch up with her!
什么？
What?
谁？
Who?
蓝钻石
Blue Diamond.
蓝钻石？
Blue Diamond?
噢，哦，不，在地球？
Oh, oh, on Earth?
我的天！
Holy smokes!
她们总算要现身了
They're all coming out of the woodwork.
紫晶，变成把椅子
Amethyst, turn into a chair.
我-我得坐下来
I-I need to sit down.
她带走了爸爸！
She took Dad!
她像外星人一样绑架了他，而这都是我的错！
She alien abducted him, and it's all my fault!
她抓走了格雷格？
She took Greg?
我们的格雷格？
Our Greg?
难道还有别的格雷格？
What other Greg is there?
我们该怎么将他带回来？
How are we gonna get him back?
她甚至要他有什么用？
What does she even want him for?
吃掉他？将他放进动物园？
To eat him? To put him in a zoo?
等等
Wait.
还真可能是这样
That might be it.
她会吃了他？！
She's gonna eat him?!
什么？不！
What? No.
但确实有个-不，不，
But there was a -- No, no.
但不可能仍然还在
It couldn't possibly still exist.
至少从我们-
Not since we --
对啊
That's right.
粉钻石隐秘的人类动物园
Pink Diamond's insidious human zoo.
什么？
What?
当她还在地球时，
During her reign on Earth,
粉钻石将人类从他们的家人旁掠走
Pink Diamond stole humans from their families
作为她征程的一个奖杯
as trophies of her conquests.
你一定是在开玩笑吧？
You got to be kidding.
哦，不
Oh, no.
这是真的
It was very serious.
当我还在服务于...母世界
When I still served... Homeworld,
我亲眼看到的
I saw it myself.
一个深空中的私人野生动物园
A private menagerie deep in space.
人类被困在其中
Humans in captivity.
我们一直没能救他们出来
We were never able to rescue them.
战争开始后我们一直没有能力接近他们
We had no way to get to them after the war.
但这是五千年前了
But that was over 5,000 years ago.
你真的确定格雷格在那里？
You really think Greg's there?
史蒂文，蓝钻石想让他活着？
Steven, Blue Diamond wanted him alive?
对，是的！她很喜欢他！
Yes, yes! She liked him!
我想不出还有什么地方她会安置他
I can't think of anywhere else she'd put him
如果她想留着他，
if she wanted to keep him.
如果动物园还在的话，
That is if the zoo's still there.
只能去那里试试了
It's our only chance.
但我们该怎么到那里？
But how are we going to get there?
用the Roaming Eye
With the Roaming Eye.
红宝石的太空船？
The Ruby ship?
对啊
That's right.
我们要前往太空了，
We're going into space,
而且我们一定要带回格雷格
and we're not coming back without Greg.
我们看看
Let's see.
你们的中子星定位器仍然在定位
Your pulsar trackers are tracking pulsars.
大气防护层看起来还能工作
The atmosphere shield seems functional,
但你们在太空中用不到那个，显然
but you're not going to need that in space, obviously.
确保这对史蒂文是安全的
Make sure it's safe for Steven.
他应该没问题，
He should be fine,
但我认为我得更改
but I think I should go in and change
红宝石们设定的系统偏好
the system preferences the Rubies set.
你感觉绿光相比红光怎么样
How do you feel about green lights instead of red?
没时间搞这些了！
There's no time for that!
如果能用的话，咱们赶紧干！
If it works, - let's just do it already!
对不起，康妮，但我们等不及了
Sorry, Connie, but we just can't wait.
爸爸身陷困境
Dad's in trouble,
而且我们得前往太空将他带回来
and we need to go into space to get him back.
没时间了
There's no time.
我们现在就走
We're going right now.
一定要在我们离开后保护好沙滩市
Just protect Beach City for me while we're gone.
那么，如果我输入坐标，
So, if I input the coordinates,
它就会直接带我们过去？
it will take us right there?
实际上更复杂一些
It's a little more complicated than that.
这不是你们那种第一代的“轻型风筝”
These aren't your era one light kites.
你们很可能会“扭曲现实”
You're gonna be pretty much bending reality
如果要用引力引擎的话
if you turn on the gravity engine.
考虑到这个，我真的该
Come to think of it, I should really change
一起更改红宝石对那个设置的偏好
the ruby preferences on that, too.
所以呢？那个设的是红色！
So what? So it's red!
快啊，快点！我们得走了！
Come on, come on! We got to go!
先不管红宝石，它能飞起来吗？
Rubies aside, will it fly?
简单来说，可以
Short answer, yes.
那么，出发！
Okay, let's go.
青金石，橄榄石，留在这里
Lapis, Peridot, stay here.
你们得保护沙滩市
You'll have to protect Beach City
以防我们离开时有事发生
if something happens while we're gone.
你们可以相信我们
You can count on us.
不要担心，爸爸
Don't worry, Dad.
我们已经在路上了
We're on our way.
我真希望他能看到这样的风景
I hope he got to see some of this.
这里的风光足够填满
There's enough out here
一整个有关宇宙的相册了
for a whole album about the cosmos.
Oh, oh!
太空涡流
Space turbulence.
飞的不错嘛
Sweet moves.
等等
Hold on.
好吧，我们还要飞多远-
All right, how much further till we get to --
啊！
Aah!
对不起，红宝石
Sorry, Rubies.
我们真的该对她们做点什么
We should really do something about them.
我们能在回来的路上接她们
We can pick them up on the way back.
爸爸是首要任务
Dad comes first.
还有多久我们能到那里？
How much longer till we get there?
呃，按现在的速度
Well, at our current speed,
我们到达人类动物园应该在...
we should be reaching the human zoo in...
大约七十人类年之后
approximately 70 human years.
刚好赶上格雷格的
Just in time for Greg's 110th anniversary
110大寿
of being alive.
珍珠，我爸的身体状况
Pearl, my dad's not healthy enough
坚持不了那么久
to live that long.
呃...你觉得我们能把时间砍到69年吗？
Uh...do you think he'll be able to make it to 109?
我们走之前
Before we left,
橄榄石提到了引力引擎
Peridot did mention a gravity engine.
哦，对啊，她说那会“扭曲现实”
Oh, yeah. She said it bends reality.
噢，我确定她是在夸大其词
Oh, I'm sure she was exaggerating.
这很可能只是改变速度的定义
It probably just alters the definition of speed
通过操纵时空来达成，
by manipulating space time,
但这对有机物质会有什么影响？
but what effect will that have on organic matter?
这有可能会扁平化史蒂文的身体
It might flatten Steven's body
将其变成由皮肤和骨骼组成的烙饼
into a pancake of skin and bones.
骨头很恶心
Bones are gross.
你卧室里可有骨头
You have bones in your bedroom.
那不一样
That's different.
那是我的骨头
Those are my bones.
如果变成烙饼能拯救我爸爸，
If being a pancake means saving my dad,
那么，端上酱汁吧
then bring on the syrup.
史蒂文
Steven.
史蒂文？你还好吗？
Steven? Are you okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
我感觉我刚刚晕了过去
I think I just blacked out.
呃，你们还好吗？
Um, are you guys okay?
你说呢？
You tell me.
呃，不，有地方不对
Uh, no, we're not okay!
呃，为什么你们看起来怪怪的？
Uh, why do you guys look like that?
引力传送似乎对我们的身体有影响
The gravity warp seems to be affecting our bodies.
一定要告诉我这会有持久的效果
Please tell me this lasts forever.
我们的身体是由光组成的，
Our bodies are made of light,
而通常光会制造出质量
and usually they form a mass
这取决于周围的气压
dependent on the air pressure
与引力状况
and the level of gravity in the environment.
但我们身处的情况
But we're in a situation
不适用于一般的物理规则
where the normal laws of physics don't apply.
谁在乎呢？反正很有趣
Who cares? It's funny.
这怎么有趣了？！
In what way is this funny?!
那么，你们不是故意这么做的？
So, you guys aren't doing this on purpose?
你们不能通过变形变回去吗？
Can't you shapeshift back?
等等
Hold on.
哈，快看，美洲狮崽
Huh, check it out. Puma cub.
飞船似乎通过散发某种能量
The ship seems to be putting out some kind of energy,
让我们保持现在的尺寸
keeping us in this shape.
哦，我知道该怎么做了
Oh, I know the problem.
真的？
You do?
橄榄石说这艘船是按红宝石校准的
Peridot said the ship was calibrated for Rubies.
这肯定让你们都变成了红宝石的大小
It must be making you all Ruby sized.
啊！为什么她从不告诉我们任何事？
Ugh! Why doesn't she ever tell us anything?
这就是为什么我们不要听她的话
This is why we don't listen to her.
也许我能更改设置
Maybe I can change the settings.
不！
No.
不是
Nope.
对不起！
Sorry!
这好像行不通
This isn't working.
试试手动调节
Try adjusting it manually.
喔，呃，也许是这个？
Whoa. Um, maybe this one?
好吧，所以它是干这个的
Okay, so that does that.
也许是这个？
Maybe this one.
啊！为什么要搞得这么复杂？
Aah! Why is this so complicated?
嘿，史蒂文
Hey, Steven.
这开始变得有点怪了，即使对我也是
This is getting a little weird, even for me.
我好像发现关闭按钮了
I think I found the off switch.
伙计们！我-我做什么了？
Guys! W-What did I do?
紫晶？石榴？珍珠？
Amethyst? Garnet? Pearl?
你们在哪？
Where are you?
发生什么了？你们碎了？
What happened? Are you cracked?
紫晶通常已经恢复了
Amethyst is usually back by now.
哦，不！那是动物园
Oh, no. That's the zoo.
呃，我们要直接跟动物园撞上了，
Uh, we're gonna smash right into it
如果还不减速的话
if we don't slow down.
上啊，史蒂文
Come on, Steven.
你能做到的
You can do it.
这没什么
It's okay.
宝石人们没事的
The gems are gonna be fine.
她们不会出事的
They got to be fine.
爸爸也不会出事的
Dad's gonna be fine, too.
虽然现在看起来不是这样，
It doesn't seem like it right now,
但待会，我们会在一起欢笑的
but later, we're gonna laugh.
只要我能让太空船停下
If I could just stop the ship.
它不会停下的
It isn't going to stop.
没法解决这个问题
There's no fixing this.
这都是我的错
It's all my fault.
我太着急了
I rushed us.
我逼着大家做出愚蠢又错误的决定
I pushed us into making stupid mistakes.
本不用这样的
It didn't have to be this way.
我本应听石榴的话
I didn't have to not listen to Garnet.
我不应去韩国
I didn't have to go to Korea.
爸爸
Dad.
我不应让你被蓝钻石永远带走
I didn't have to get you taken away forever by Blue Diamond.
我-我不是出于自私
I-I wasn't trying to be selfish.
我这次只是想搞清都发生了什么
I just wanted to know what was going on for myself for once.
但现在我失去了所有人
But now I lost everyone.
爸爸！
Dad!
我想我的爸爸！
I want my dad!
我只想见到我爸！
I just want my dad.
你们回来了！
You're back!
之前去哪了？
Where'd you go?
我之前非常担心！
I was so worried!
我想你试图恢复我们身体的举动
I think in your attempt to fix our bodies,
也许意外的
you may have accidentally
关闭了所有的校准
shut off the calibration altogether.
我们由光组成的外形无法跟上
Our light-composed forms couldn't keep up with a ship
超过光速移动的飞船
moving faster than the speed of light.
所以你们刚才只是一直落在飞船后方？
So you were just lagging behind the ship this whole time?
是啊，不要太担心
Yeah. Don't worry about it too much.
紫晶很喜欢这样
Amethyst liked it.
我从没想到我能伸展到那么远
I never thought I could stretch so far.
我感觉我貌似直接贯穿了某个星球！
I think I kind of phased through a planet.
呃，史小子
Uh, yo, Ste-man.
你听到石榴说的话了
You heard Garnet.
我们完全没事，哥们
We're totally fine, dude.
我-我太心急了，我-
I-I was pushing so hard,I-
我只是非常想见到我爸爸
I just wanted to get Dad back so much.
我-我几乎搞砸了整个任务
I-I almost wrecked the mission.
这都是我的错
This whole thing is my fault.
史蒂文，不是你绑架的格雷格
Steven, you didn't kidnap Greg.
是蓝钻石做的
Blue Diamond did.
喔，你们看到了吗？
Whoa. Do you guys see that?
你所做的带我们到了动物园
What you did got us to the zoo.
是吗？
Yeah?
而且只是提前了70人类年而已
And only 70 human years ahead of schedule.
我很快会见到你的，爸爸
I'll see you really soon, Dad.
我希望
I hope.